Thank you so much for taking the time to meet today.
I'm so excited.
Yeah, where are you located on it?
Where are you sitting?
Right now, right now, I'm actually in Copenhagen.
So I'm a little bit older than normal.
Yes.
Oh, my, see, I'm up here on the beach.
It's your mind.
Actually, I'm not.
I love it.
I like to be on the beach right now, but I'm here in my office.
Unfortunately.
Ah, okay.
If you're old to be on it, join us at your moments.
Okay, perfect.
That sounds good.
Now, I love the way you're, you're did the website.
I like the concept, the, it was bright.
It was precise.
And you did a good job not knowing any of the point we're doing.
Just for looking on the website.
I mean, did a awesome job.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Um, I've had, I had a lot of fun with it.
It was, it was a great, it was a great opportunity for me to do something
a little bit new.
So thank you for giving me that opportunity.
What are you doing in Copenhagen?
Um, so actually, I've been a kitesurfing in Spain.
And then I just came up to Copenhagen for a couple of days just to check it out.
Oh, so were you in Spain or nearly all the time, huh?
Yes.
Yeah.
What are you doing in Spain?
I was kitesurfing.
Hi, surfing.
Yes.
How about that?
Now, where do you live?
I am from Colorado.
Oh, so what are having fun then?
I am.
Yes.
I just had to, I just graduated from, um, being University of Michigan.
So I'm taking my little break.
Oh, yeah.
With Macy and all the girls there.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's what family, yeah.
Oh, yes.
That's awesome.
What was your major there?
I'm down to analytics.
So I was coding.
Wow.
But you did kitesurfing in Spain, huh?
Yes.
I did.
It was, it was a great, it was a great opportunity.
I bet it was.
It was fun to do too.
I did.
Yes.
Yeah.
It was awesome.
Hi Julie, how are you?
I'm great.
How are you?
Thank you.
Are you back from Spain?
Are you still there?
I'm in Copenhagen now.
We're just kind of jumping around for a little bit.
Wow.
Well, thank you for making time for us.
I so appreciate it.
I know this is probably not at the top of your priority, but we really appreciate all that
you've done.
It's at the top of my priority.
I'm so excited to be meeting with you all.
Good.
Okay.
Well, we love your website.
We've got, um, I've got Donna and Jennifer here.
I will show you them.
Hang on.
I know.
I don't know why that is that it didn't go through for the Zoom invite, but they are.
Yeah.
Bye bye.
Hello.
Um, do you want me to try to put her on here so you'll can see her?
Sure.
Okay.
But then I can't pull up.
So there were a few things that we had talked about that Dr. Festy had, um, I think wanted, um,
well, Dr. Festy, do you want to walk through what you were, uh, talking about?
And then at, you know, I had kind of gone over and sort of, you used what you said and tried to rework them a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, I'm trying to miss you where I find it, where I had it all listed.
Let's see here.
Hang on.
And if it's okay, I'm recording this meeting just if that's, if that's all right.
Okay.
Sure.
Thank you.
Good.
Well, let me find what I have here.
Go back.
One thing.
Yeah.
Um, in the first part, um, I tried to print on this up so I could have the website up at the same time.
But I can't.
I mean, let me, actually, let me just try to do that real quick.
Let's take the new up.
Yeah, you can sit over here.
Okay.
All right.
So, you know, on the first page, you're journey to optimal vitality.
I mean, I guess, are you kind of, well, first let's talk.
Do you want to like kind of go through this with us hourly?
I know we kind of pay to the initial, but if you want to help us just make some changes.
We'd like to make it like over the next week if that's possible.
The 100%.
Yes.
That sounds great.
Okay.
And then one of our patients was talking about EOS.
Do you know anything about that?
Like the, it's like, you know, it's like privacy.
And I, you know, I, I guess we just need to make sure that.
From a privacy standpoint.
Yeah.
Let's hit the compliant.
But if you connect it, you know, I guess that's just something to consider and look into if we connect to the.
So.
I got a couple questions about that as well.
But we can talk about that later just with the patient portal and connecting everything like that.
I just want to make sure that I understand everything that you guys use before I connect.
Like the back end and everything like that.
But we can go over that after if you'd like.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
So I, you know, you had put integrated regenerative and preventive medicine built on 50 years of clinical foundation and the long view of whole body health from the inside out.
I was, I had kind of looked at a couple of different things.
And you guys tell me what if you like these are not.
I do like that.
But these are a couple of different options.
True health begins beneath the surface.
We practice integrated regenerative and preventive medicine and drawing on half a century of clinical wisdom to help you heal, strengthen and thrive from the inside out.
I like that.
I mean, these are all applaud, but they are just kind of like, you know, putting in kind of a little more of what.
And the other option was you're more than a symptom or integrated regenerative and preventive approach draws on 50 years of clinical care to support your whole health body mind and long term vitality.
Do you, do you guys like any of those Dr. Festy or do you like that?
I like that.
Okay.
The first one of the second one.
I like the second one.
It's drawing my eye more.
Is it?
Yeah.
These two option.
Oh, okay.
I was thinking that we were more than a symptom.
I tried to print them out so you guys could all see that we're, and about we're so busy.
We just, it's like we're going to fit it in.
So I can't even imagine.
No, I can't imagine.
Don't, don't worry.
Anyway, those are a couple of things that we might change.
Yeah.
Do you like body and long term vitality?
I like that.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's like going more.
So option B.
You are more than a symptom.
Are integrated.
Or do you like that as the catch line for the very first page though?
Kind of.
Yeah.
Or is that where are we talking?
Okay.
You've seen the website right now.
Yeah.
I know.
You can what?
I can share my screen.
So I think it's part.
Yeah.
Right there.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's do this.
So integrated regenerative and preventive medicine builds on 50 years of clinical foundation in the long view.
Okay.
That versus.
I thought I was sure about the whole body health.
Yeah.
You know,
I'm inside out.
I mean, that's okay.
But I'm going to think about whether we change.
I thought sure what we suggested to change, but maybe something to think about.
Okay.
I kind of like true health begins beneath the surface.
We practice integrated regenerative.
Yeah.
That's good.
Clinical wisdom to help you heal strengthen and thrive or help.
I don't know.
We can work on that.
But that's something that we're going to have to change in.
And about if you.
I need to understand how to make some changes.
You gave me access, but.
Yes.
And people to like fully edit it or how that.
Okay.
So I would just go in like you're going in.
And if we want to tweak it, I can go in and do that.
100%.
Yes.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Website on.
It's on.
It's called Webflow.
So yeah.
It's the easiest for you to be able to manage without having to deal with the code or anything like that.
And then Rob and I had a call last week as well.
And he mentioned you all being like wanting to do promotions or things like that on the website or like.
Just being able to edit a little bit more easily.
So you would also allow you to do that there as well.
And pretty easily.
And I can.
I can make like a zoom tutorial.
And so that you can watch it whenever you want to add a promotion or anything like that.
That'd be great.
Okay.
All right.
Now on the services part.
And.
Dr. Festy you do have yours up on services.
Trying to find it here.
Do the hang on.
I got so much going on in my laptop.
Again, you find everything.
I mean, hang on.
Let me see if I can find it.
Hang on.
Nope.
That's not it.
Let's see here.
So on services.
Annabelle, what did you have?
Can you go to services?
Yep.
Interest.
Can you see my screen still?
Yeah.
Okay.
So I'm on services.
Which part?
Okay.
So we wanted five pillars because he wanted to add some of the DNA testing.
To that.
Yeah.
The thing about it is that there's a lot of things we do in peptide hormone weight loss and wellness.
There's a slew of testing we do for all sorts of problems.
I'm just wondering whether that might be an area that we'd add in as far as the fifth sections.
Considering.
Okay.
Section number five.
Yeah.
I think.
Okay.
So I think advanced diagnostics and early detection might be a fifth.
Fifth.
Fifth one.
Yes.
Yeah.
And you could put in a DNA testing.
Gallery multi a cancer early detection.
Glycane.
Next.
Yeah.
Next gen.
Of course, the gin testing.
Yeah.
And I'll go stand like an age.
I mean, all these things we do for different testing would be nice to have as a fifth pillar.
Okay.
So we'll and I'll send you a list of all of those so that you can easily add that.
So you'll kind of understand what they are and everything.
Great.
Yeah.
And then.
Let's see.
And the services intro.
Where's the services intro on the site.
Right here.
So this would be that paragraph.
Petite therapy.
Therapy hormone optimization, medical weight loss and wellness and rejuvenation prescribed against.
First.
Fifth one.
We just talked about.
Yes.
Fifth one.
Okay.
So then I would.
I think that one to this as well.
Do you want to change the wording or the intro as a whole?
I just didn't like and I knew it's like it is.
It's a good way to say it, but I'm not sure that all of our patients are going to understand like prescribed against your physiology.
And so I just thought maybe changing that wording a tiny bit and you know.
I mean, it's it makes a lot of sense, but it just kind of I don't know.
100%.
Yep.
For sure.
So five pillars changing that wording a tiny bit.
What about you guys?
Did you see it?
It shows the five pillars.
Well, she's going to add it here.
I just figured one over here.
Yeah.
Can you show can you scroll down for the four pillars?
I don't need it is.
I know.
Karma.
Like weight loss.
And then the fifth one would be down here right now.
What is going on this one?
Like being a advanced testing.
Do you like that?
I don't know.
So you're going to publish.
We don't have to do pillars.
You can.
This is all.
Did you not get the website?
I'd send it to you.
We were just to take notes for this.
So that just the notes that we that Dr. Festy had come up with.
And we kind of adding I kind of changed it a little bit.
What do you think?
I have to go through it all.
Okay.
So this is what it is.
This if you can look at here.
Also at the beginning in a bill.
It's a 60 minute consultation not 90.
Okay.
So this would be five.
This is how it looks.
Okay.
There's the four.
Yeah.
And then she would just add advanced testing here.
And then I also wanted to clarify the complimentary consultation.
Sorry.
What?
The complimentary consultation is something you still provide.
Yes.
Okay.
Great.
That just not 90 minutes.
Okay.
I've practiced built on legacy a future built on you.
I love that.
That's so good.
I don't know how to operate the strong clinical foundations established by our founder, Dr. Joseph S.D.
While he is no longer seeing patients and is now an administrative and advisory role here.
I mean, it's a guiding source of research inside an educational leadership as we carry for his 50 years fix for peace.
I love that.
Do you like that Dr. Festy?
Yes, I do.
That's fine.
Sure.
Okay.
And I love this.
I want to read some more like a relationship than an appointment measurement date.
Yeah.
That's the right theory in my picture.
I had mentioned that there's a, there's a link we could do to my CV, which is 55 pages that people like to look at occasionally to see what's happened in the past.
So you just put a little link there says link to whatever the CV.
So like that.
Yeah.
So 56 years of all of this.
Well, there's one place in here that says that this clinic is 56 years old.
This clinic is not his, his.
No.
His.
No B G I N and fertility.
But so the, so the experience is 50 over 50 years of experience, but not the clinic itself.
Okay.
And then we can send you his CV so you could just add a link to that.
And then I'll be tweak mine a little bit.
Yeah.
Give you your and carry my tweak hers.
Okay.
And then as far as your headshots, do you have ones that would fit.
Yeah.
Where are those?
Do we have?
I can send this to my.
Okay.
Yeah.
She'll send.
Here's with good.
Thank all of her good, Julie.
They're all above all three of you all three women.
We're good.
Headshots.
Yeah.
So, although mine's AI and my girls are like, it's so obviously AI, but nobody
art.
Yeah.
So.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I was fine with it.
All right.
Start with the complementing consultation.
And this says 30 minutes.
So you need to put that makes 60 minutes on that one.
Is this.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Right there.
So all the consultations are 60 minutes.
Right.
Okay.
That's not every page.
So I need to change that.
All right.
That sounds good.
Okay.
And then services menu.
So we're going to change that to five pillars.
Do you like that?
The five pillars?
I think it looks cool.
It is cool.
And we need to add all of our peptides.
I think.
Yeah.
All the peptides exactly.
Can you send a list of all of the peptides?
Absolutely.
And maybe add some of the work and say that we all, we have more.
Because there's so many that the way of keeping up with all of them.
But we also have to make sure we're not marketing it.
We have to say it the right way.
And I think you did say it the right way.
And about where it's not like you can't really advertise peptides
because some of them are not FDA approved.
So you have to prescribe.
Let's see.
I think I like how you can read all of them on one little.
I know.
I do too.
It's really well.
I had put on the peptide intro.
Peptide therapy works best when it's personal.
At vital health, every treatment is guided by your labs.
Oops.
And hang on.
I just went away.
Well.
So your labs and goals recommended only when you're full clinical picture supports it.
You'd like to be right here in the description.
Great.
I meant that the stimulate cellular regrow system is targeted.
I think that we have to do something like that
because we can't advertise that it stimulates cellular regrow.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
That's just legally like a regulatory standpoint.
It's really supposed to say it does this.
You can say in these worlds, it's thought to do that, you know.
So.
Okay.
So it works.
Yeah.
Um.
Okay.
And then.
Are we going too fast or is it okay since you're bringing.
Okay.
On the hormones section.
Can you go there?
Yeah.
Under the, for instance, under the, under the women.
Is that as much as almost ninety percent,
a hundred percent are without testosterone at menopause.
And so it could vary fifty percent between the age of twenty and fifty,
but after menopause,
a hundred percent lack of testosterone.
Yeah.
We could put that in there.
I had said.
Let's see you.
Okay.
So on hormone optimization,
bioidentical hormone therapy for men and women,
the long view of hormone picture tested quarterly and adjusted at microdose precision.
I do like that.
Yeah.
Uh.
I Dr.
Fessie had kind of wanted some of the symptoms in there.
So not necessarily, I kind of like what you have there,
but somewhere maybe something hormones touch nearly everything.
If you're struggling with sleep, weight, energy, libido,
migraines, depression, hot flashes, night sweats or difficult periods,
your hormones are likely involved.
Yeah.
I think so much that you really added to for women and for men.
It's not going to be, you know,
probably involving basically fatigue, libido issues,
probably involving high cholesterol, high LDL.
I mean, like a list of other things for men too,
as far as symptoms are concerned.
Yeah.
Okay.
You have tried under what we treat.
She does have a lot of that under what we treat.
Um.
Well, what we treat is different than symptoms.
That's good.
Well, maybe not.
I guess it'd be okay.
It tells you like, you like this one.
Like how it says fatigue.
Yeah.
Like a emotional to you kind of.
So in about that sentence that I just said, I'll send you,
I'll send you my little PDF and I'll circle the things that we are
talking about that we like.
Okay.
Um.
And then, you know, there's also.
We're seeing that.
Let's do it.
I never seen it on a vaginal dryness.
It's very common.
Very, I don't know.
That's the symptom that I just have.
And then by identical therapy protects post menopausal women against
heart disease, dementia, urinary incontinence, college and loss and skin elasticity.
They may also experience fatigue, disrupted sleep, weight gain, metabolic
changes, vaginal dryness, painful intercourse, mood changes, anxiety, depression.
I mean, it's like a whole list speaks to me because.
Yeah.
Because it's like people that are like, oh, now I get it.
But you didn't know what it was.
Yeah.
Right.
So I'll give you that list and see if we can incorporate, just make it, you
have a lot of it on there, but maybe not all of it.
And we'll see if we can incorporate some of that.
Yeah.
And a third column or third.
So over here, maybe.
Okay.
Now since the very first ball of pace, 90 minutes for the first visit,
should we change the course 60 minutes?
Yes.
I have that noted.
Okay.
And then.
Also, one thing I thought might be important, hormonal imbalances don't
only affect older women, adolescents and young adults experience PMS,
thyroid issues, PCOS, which is now different.
Or infertility are also candidates for careful hormonal, hormonal
support.
Yeah.
Do you like that?
Dr.
Festy.
Okay.
I'll like that.
Yeah.
I can relate to them.
And then for men.
I thought somewhere we could put testosterone, DHEA, thyroid,
and cortisol are interdependent.
A shift in one reshapes the others.
Men's hormone, optimization at vital health begins with
comprehensive labs and targets lean muscle, libido, cognitive
function, cardiovascular protection, and long horizon vitality.
Yeah.
I like it better.
Because that one shifts the rest follows with a little bit different
to how long the way you, what you said it.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then I gave a list of everything that men with low testosterone
can experience.
Right.
Okay.
So Annabelle, this might be kind of what?
Even the men that.
Cause I don't have that.
That's good too.
Like that.
Okay.
Under the man.
Under man.
It's like fatigue and low energy, reduced libido and sexual
dysfunction, loss of lean muscle mass, increased body fat
particularly around the abdomen, brain fog and difficulty
training, mood changes, irritability and depression.
Of course, sleep in insomnia, decreased bone density,
hair thinning, reduced motivation and drive and cardiovascular
changes and decreased stamina.
Yeah.
I think I'll send this is a lot.
And I'm also I'll just send you this whole PDF and circle kind of
what we would love to incorporate.
If it doesn't make sense, I don't know how difficult it is to
add all this stuff to the website.
So you have to guide us to and what you can reasonably do
and what you can't.
Yeah.
This is all a very.
Attable.
Okay.
Yeah.
This won't take very long.
Okay.
All right.
Good.
I had a testimonial section down here on the home page.
Is this something that you guys wanted to include or do you want me to
remove it?
I love that.
Yes.
Love it.
We have a lot of testimonials we can put in there.
Yeah.
We could put more in there if you want to because we have over
85 or 95 star reviews.
Awesome.
We can have it could be like a moving thing of all of the moving
slides are almost of all of the reviews if you'd like that.
Good luck.
People love to see five star reviews that they go by that a lot
and make a decision to come in.
So that's why I think we've nice to have all the five star
reviews.
Like you said, maybe it could be shown with this slide
through it or whatever it may take.
But well, it should do help a lot for people coming
into the clinic.
Awesome.
Let's add it.
That sounds great.
Can you add it where it every time somebody adds a new review
it automatically goes on the website.
For sure.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
That would be great.
Okay.
And then the shop.
Do we have that on there?
I know.
I'm just going to ask about that.
Okay.
We would love to add a supplement shop.
Yeah.
So we have to apply currently.
Sorry.
Yeah.
I can see.
So we do.
We do currently have the Shopify.
But I'm not sure.
We don't have a lot of supplements.
And we can't legally add a lot of our supplements.
So I'm not sure what we can do on that.
Why can't we legally add them?
They won't allow us to add them without private labeling them.
We're like a lot of our private labeling.
So we are.
We have five or six right now.
Oh, but we can't do the rest.
We can't.
We can.
Can we not just sell them non private label on our.
I mean, it like.
We can list a brand.
We can't list the supplements.
Transformation.
Like this is transformation.
Let's ask.
Orthomolecular does not.
Quicksilver does not.
We have to privately label all this.
So if you're private label.
So okay.
If you're private label.
General Jennifer.
It can get pricey.
But yeah, we can do that.
Well, I mean, to me, we should privately label all of
anywhere.
I think it'd be good idea.
When did I get it anywhere else?
You know, we could probably be able to one of them would be nice.
It's just nice and about because we do a lot of ours on telehealth.
And so when I'm talking to patients and I recommend, you know, vitamin D3 with K or,
you know, our methyl B vitamins, like it would be easy for me to say,
hey, just go to our shop.
I'll put it in.
But what's happening now is they're like, oh, I can't really
come into the office.
I'll just order on Amazon.
And we really don't want that.
You know, we want them to use what we're using.
Great.
So, okay.
So when you say that you want them to be able to add it to the cart,
that would have to come directly from what do you like when they
order it?
What do you recommend they order it from?
That's not Amazon.
Do you have an example?
Have it here in package it here.
And we have, we were going to get all that.
We have a big supply.
We have a huge supply room that we can package it and send it out if they
order it.
But I guess we could connect to Amazon and then I don't know.
Can you bet it?
I don't know.
Yeah.
We're not going to do Amazon it first.
We're just going to do Shopify.
We're going to use Shopify.
And we use our own substance and we order it through the company.
And then they order through us.
And then it's like your party seller pretty much.
Okay.
So everything is on Shopify that people would want to buy.
Then we could connect the Shopify.
Let me look into it.
But I think we could connect Shopify to Webflow.
And.
Okay.
Let me think about that.
But yes.
Yeah.
How we're doing it now.
There's another software involved in it.
Okay.
I just can't think of because it's job.
Why?
The payment.
Okay.
Well, you guys work on that and then let her know.
I don't know anything about that part.
Yeah.
So I think it would be ideal if we could do it.
But I don't.
It's not.
Yeah.
I don't know how to make it happen.
Oh, closer.
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
Yeah.
We use Clover.
Clover.
Yeah.
That's who ships the products to the patients.
No, we do.
That's our.
Shopify.
Well, we we ship it.
Okay.
Just for.
Clover is the payment system.
Uh,
on the website.
Our website is on words.
It's a it's a whole thing.
Okay.
If you found an easier way, please let us know.
That's just all we we've been told.
Okay.
Got it.
Yeah.
Let me look into that.
There's definitely an easier way.
I just need to do a little bit of research before I speak on it.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Um, but yeah.
I mean, I think do you guys have other.
I said so.
I mean, essentially we're going to change a little bit of the wording.
We're going to add a fifth parallel.
We're going to kind of create the symptoms for men and women that they might be going through.
We're going to add advanced diagnostics and early detection.
Pillar with DNA testing.
Gallery multi cancer early detection.
Glycan age.
Next gen.
Cognitive.
And more.
And then try to work on the shop.
But does anybody else have it?
Like does that?
Is there anything else that you when looking at the website that you were worried about or wanted to?
So are I go back to the first page.
If you could.
Very first page.
Where's my butterfly going to be?
It's a.
I'm going to fly in there for one up there in the upper left hand side though.
But we don't make one that's alive.
That.
That flutters and you could.
We have one on our website is a.
It's a colored one on the very end of our website.
There are two of them.
There's a one the first part in the one the last part.
Little bitty little bitty one that you could be fluttering up there in the corner if you wanted to.
Alive.
I got one.
You've got one.
We could try to make it.
I actually saw a hummingbird outside the window today that you would love it.
I think it's like Dr.
Best of you would love looking at it right over there.
Stick up enough there.
Yeah.
Um.
You go to.
A lot of love.
Are we going to put our love on the website?
Yeah.
Oh.
It just needs to be bigger.
I think maybe the vital health and the hummingbird should be bigger.
So the.
I think exactly right.
Yeah.
So for older eyes.
You can't see like you guys can't.
I can do that.
That sounds good.
Yeah.
People forget that.
And we also need to take out since nineteen.
Yeah.
That's the same.
Okay.
Perfect.
Um.
Okay.
And then as far as the patient portal goes, is it okay that it connects to this for now or would.
Nice.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Okay.
Yeah.
We just have to figure out.
How are we doing it now?
It's in the order form.
We need to add the order form.
Yeah.
Patients can order their their stuff online.
Where do you think it should be?
It can probably be right next to the patient portal.
You can say like order form or.
So right next to patient portal.
Put order or.
Order order order form something.
Reorder form.
Order.
I don't know.
Something.
We can word it.
But yeah.
Um.
We have it on our current website.
Yeah.
How do we.
It does like hormone reorder form.
It's in the left corner.
When you click.
Yeah.
Hormone reorder.
Okay.
And that is.
Yeah.
And you can probably make it look a little better.
Sure.
Okay.
Cool.
And then this is the shop you're talking about.
Yes.
Yeah.
We only have about 25 or 30 submits on there.
All private label.
And I think that would be a good idea.
Jennifer.
How how expensive is it for private label?
It can get pretty pricey.
You have to order at least 40 at one time.
And then there's also a startup fee.
So I'll get all that information.
I'll send it to you.
Yeah.
I think probably private label would be good for it.
So sure.
Do you think so?
Yeah.
Yes.
Um.
Is patient is connecting it to servo with patient.
Is it patient.
Information.
We got to make sure that's a clean.
Oh, so the servo is.
It's a big appliance.
Yeah.
What about your board website?
She said to talk about direct EOS.
What would you say in the beginning?
I don't know.
It was what.
Thank you.
Gary was talking about that.
Yeah.
I don't know.
There's, you know,
there's something.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
Don't you think that would be for the actual log-in part?
Yeah.
So when they're in that log-in, they're safe.
Like, yeah.
That's why I haven't touched this.
So I think that that still is EOS compliant.
It's encrypted.
Yeah.
So I don't think I think that we're safe on all of those.
I just thought maybe we should look into it just to make sure.
So we'll look into that.
I'll look into it too.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
Okay.
And then if we can add those IV services.
Oh, yeah.
No, she has it to here.
Can you show her that IVs weren't they on there?
I thought they were.
There are other website.
I think.
I believe.
On your website.
I think they are.
No, those are on our website.
Yes.
But if we can add them to the new one.
Oh, this one.
IV therapy.
Yeah.
One.
Okay.
Ivy menu.
Yeah.
I think we need to advertise that we have ozone and the nutritional
IVs.
Yeah.
That wasn't so.
The IVs and ozone need to be their own like their own.
I mean,
Yeah.
Is there a category?
Cause ozone can also be rectal and vaginal.
Yeah.
Not just Ivy.
And exesomes.
And exesomes as well.
Yeah.
Regenerative medicine.
Would that be here?
Or would that need to be?
Does any of your own separate pillar?
Yeah.
So she does have it here.
It's just it's just not as prominent.
So we need to make that a little more prominent.
Like the.
The vital health.
I mean,
you extend see on X.
Yeah.
And also Julie,
when you do a little baby,
a little discussion about the value of ozone.
whether it's the protocols,
just the value.
Why we want the use for ozone is used for as well as Ivy.
Like Ivy drips would be used for.
Yeah.
We've poured it in the same way.
We do the peptide.
Since it, you know,
we've heard it like not saying that it's proven to do this,
but it's, you know,
so we'll work at the correct way.
Yeah.
Do you want the Ivy section to be like a sixth pillar?
Or do you just want me to emphasize it more in this section?
I think so.
Because we're trying to build that Ivy room.
But I kind of like it as well.
As soon as the rejuvenation on its own,
because then it kind of almost stands out more.
And then because there's so many Ivy's,
I feel like it wouldn't get lost.
I feel like six pillars are going to get lost.
But this,
when they scroll down,
it's going to have another hole, you know.
Yeah.
So would.
So as well as in rejuvenation part of the pillars.
Yes.
That's the fourth pillar.
Okay.
So that would.
So it is with it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Just.
I like to page that about right where you look at exosomes.
It says there that.
Going back in there.
They're approximately.
Nope.
No.
Go down if you would.
Go down.
There we go.
Some more.
Some more down.
There we go.
Down a little bit more.
Where it's an exosomeous plane.
It's actually.
7% by.
At birth up.
But by age 30,
it drops down 90%.
Ah, okay.
So 90% the exosome.
The stem cells.
I mean drop down 90%.
That's why we don't use stem cells after age 30.
But we can use exosomes to the to the die.
Okay.
The doctor.
Can we.
You can.
Is there like a study that we can go to when they say that?
Like where did you get that information?
Is there a study that proves that?
Like we need to be able to.
prove it to because it because from a regulatory standpoint, you know,
we have to save like from this study or whatever.
You know,
well,
I think that information came from a certain study.
I look it up because it's been our,
in my slides for almost five years about the fact that he's 30.
It drops down 90%.
The stem cells.
Not the exosomes.
Yeah.
Just look it out.
Get on there if we have a legitimate source for it.
Yeah.
And we can also put on there too.
It's a really interesting.
There's a,
as a,
maybe a icon that says,
if you want to know about exosomes,
here's a 45 page dissertation all about exosomes,
which I have,
I've used before.
We can,
we can actually,
if they want to,
to relate to that,
they can actually click on a detailed explanation of exosomes.
They want to.
We can do that.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
The plasma as well.
Oh, yeah.
That's a big one.
Young plasma also is a big one.
Yeah.
Right.
You want that in this section as well?
Yes.
Okay.
What exosomes,
I guess.
Yeah.
Okay.
I think that's all I can think of.
Yeah.
We have the cognitive you do.
We have the carotid on there.
Did you have the carotid ultrasound on there?
Yeah.
That should be.
Um,
what else did we get?
We have,
we had that.
Beautiful.
That's the product.
That's the carotid ultrasound.
Yeah.
We're talking about the answer.
HRV.
HRV that we need that on there.
Oh, yeah.
Body con.
And body con.
And where would that be?
That would probably be part of the report.
Well,
we put that as part of our hormone program.
So maybe as part of the testing.
Maybe part of advanced testing.
Yeah.
And it's testing.
That's the best place to put it.
Yeah.
Let me,
where would that be on your, um,
website?
Not on our current website.
Okay.
Yeah.
When you send me those notes, will you just include like what,
um, the description that you'd like for that part?
Yes.
Okay.
Great.
Thank you.
And do you want that in the wellness and rejuvenation section as well?
Or?
Yeah.
That would be part of the best testing.
Advanced.
Yeah.
Combat view.
HRV in body.
That's advanced.
Yeah.
Great.
Okay.
So do you want that in like a separate tab up here?
Um,
um,
doesn't it already have its own filler?
Don't we have the filler?
The pillars are peptide, hormone, weight loss, wellness and rejuvenation.
And,
again,
Okay.
Yeah.
So that will be added there.
Okay.
Last thing.
Yeah.
Again.
And she has it on there.
She also has next gym.
Yeah.
She has all that.
But I mean,
I can't make sure.
I have this little thing.
Nutritional injections.
I don't know if we have that.
We've got health.
Heavy metal testing.
Oh, yeah.
Um,
uh,
a box,
PRP.
Um,
but that's not,
uh,
Botox and PRP aren't there during test.
So heavy metal testing and,
um,
I map.
The I'm a G.
Yeah.
And
the,
and the gene test.
The gene test.
We do a 60 gene test.
We do the gallery test.
We do the next gene test.
And then we're going to offer a full body MRI,
if we want to as far as
further investigation,
dissipating point.
How much you want to put on here?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll send,
I'll send you all of these notes,
kind of with these additions that are,
like,
kind of.
A lot.
Yeah.
A lot of them.
That's right.
Offer a lot.
Yeah.
Like those we don't,
you know,
it's not like we do them all the time,
but we have the capability.
And we'd like to,
you know,
for sure.
That makes sense.
Okay.
Yeah.
That sounds great.
I have the basic notes and then everything else.
What I would love it if you could send it over.
And then I can add it and then send it back to you.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
And then as far as Instagram goes,
do you want to have that in a separate meeting?
Do you want to talk about that in a separate meeting?
Or what are your thoughts on that?
And
I think I like both.
No.
My next patient is in 30 minutes.
So I have time.
If you have time,
Annabelle,
we would love to talk about it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
And I have my,
I'm going to go get Addie because she,
my little 14 year old daughter is so interested in this too.
And I showed her everything that you've had.
And she was like, oh, that's so cool.
So I want her to listen.
But you guys start talking.
And I'll.
So Jennifer,
do you want to,
do you want to get over there with Jennifer?
You want to get over there with Jennifer?
Are you all going to hear me sit there?
Um,
awesome.
Let me just pull up.
Um,
okay.
Perfect.
So I kind of just want to get a little bit of an understanding of what your,
what everybody's goals are with the Instagram.
I think we can kind of go in a variety of different directions with social media.
So I just kind of want to get another standing of your thoughts and desires.
So I sent Julie,
I'll share my spring again,
just a second.
Um,
this,
and as far as like wording and everything,
like that goes don't,
you don't need to look at that.
But,
um,
that obviously be changed.
Um,
but this is kind of what,
like the general,
I guess vibe would be of the first Instagram post that I just curated pretty quickly.
Um,
just to kind of see what your guys' thoughts were.
this one is like a six,
um,
it's called the carousel.
This is a six carousel,
like grouping of images,
you know,
when you scroll through.
Um,
and this would be like the introduction post,
or like,
I have noticed that you don't have any Instagram posts right now.
So I think that this would be giving,
um,
a little bit more of an introduction as to what vital help does.
Um,
and I think that would be a good first place to begin.
and then I think the Instagram,
it could be helpful just to have it as like a place where people can come
and kind of understand all of the services you all provide.
So I was kind of thinking that we could go more of that angle.
Um,
and then I also wanted to hear your guys' thoughts and feedback as well.
Well,
Annabelle,
I have done about four,
uh,
podcasts,
and then I have put them on Instagram and TikTok.
Awesome.
Now,
what I want to do is every Monday,
I want to publish a,
a podcast on all the different subjects I can think of.
So that would be go on for months.
Now, when I tried to publish them,
then turn out too good as far as now to put them on Instagram and TikTok.
I could put them on Instagram,
but I didn't know how to put them on TikTok as well.
Okay.
But I do think that every Monday morning,
I would create a podcast.
And the podcast would then be published for that day.
So for a while there,
everybody was looking for the next podcast until I stopped.
So people got to the point they were looking for the next one.
So I can keep that up on a regular basis.
See.
The second thing I want to do is a live,
I will live webinar.
Or so that I would,
for instance, I would have Julie in there
and we would talk about different things.
Or I have invited guests to come in.
But Dr. Hesse,
do you want those on,
um,
I mean,
I think that we should start the Instagram kind of with the posts,
like just regular posts,
and then your web,
like you're,
you're,
you know,
after a couple of the main ones,
I mean,
a couple of the first ones,
like one, two, three,
and then a live one from you.
And then, you know,
every Monday we can start doing it.
But I,
um,
I think that when we need to start our Instagram,
I think it needs to have like some of our,
like exactly what we do.
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So,
you know,
you're specific ones are super interesting.
And I love those.
And I think those would be great.
A little bit further down the line,
just in a few weeks.
But right.
For the first ones,
I think just a big picture of what we do is better.
Yeah.
A good idea.
Start with exactly.
Yeah.
Okay.
That sounds good.
Great.
Um,
so I think the first one,
this was kind of meant to be like one post and that people would slide through.
It's called a carousel.
Um,
and so I was thinking that for the first post,
you would have like a little bit of an introduction.
What vital help does.
Just kind of the idea,
the general gist of,
um,
the idea and the values behind,
vital health.
And then the next couple would maybe be about the different services that you all offer.
Um,
and just so that when people search you on Instagram,
they're able to get a general feel for what your business is about.
Um,
and what services you can offer them.
And then maybe after we describe all of the services you all offer,
then you could begin your, um,
Monday posts or throughout posting all of the services that you all offer.
We could include the Monday posts or the pod,
castor the webinars,
things like that.
Um,
does that sound okay?
Sure does.
Absolutely.
Okay.
And do you all know how frequently you would want to be posting on Instagram ideally?
Uh,
every day.
I'll just kidding.
As much as possible.
Okay.
Um,
I think the most,
the more we do,
the better I would think anyway,
to me.
Okay.
We only have like two other patients on there.
Not even patients.
We're just writing people.
Totally.
But, um,
one thing I think,
you know,
I,
I am about asked if we had pictures that we wanted to use.
And I said,
not at this point,
but I know that we've talked about,
I love the ones that you pay,
because they're the least stocky looking,
but they still are,
they're still,
you know,
they're not,
are clinic obviously.
So,
I don't know if you guys,
if we want to get a photographer
and kind of take pictures of people in our clinic,
and then have her use those before she starts,
you know,
to kind of welcome everybody to the new office.
This is our office and have more of our stuff in there.
I don't know.
You don't think an idea.
Um,
or do you want to just start with like this?
These are great.
They're beautiful.
They are beautiful.
Also,
I think a thing on social media right now is,
I'm not sure how you guys feel,
but it's not like the,
you don't need to have a photographer come and take pictures
if you didn't want to.
Like,
it would also be cool if you just took like a video
and just did like a little introduction of like what the office
looked like,
or just take a couple of pictures of your own phone.
I don't want you to feel pressured to like get a photographer
because I think people will still love to just see what it's like
from your perspective.
Um,
just like,
this is when you walk into the office.
Just random videos showing off the new space in general.
I think could also be very valuable.
Okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
So,
we can make some of those and send them to you.
That sounds great.
Did you get to play with?
Yeah.
That sounds awesome.
And then as far so everyday posting,
um,
am I,
do you want me to,
send those to somebody and then they post them,
um,
themselves and maybe,
how would I just,
I think you want to do a week or once a week?
I don't,
I don't think every,
I think that like,
at least twice a week.
Yeah.
Okay.
Two to three times a week.
Three times a week is ideal.
And then they would send them,
she would send them to Jennifer.
Right.
Are you going to be in charge of it or?
Yeah.
Or Scott.
And we'll figure that out.
We'll figure it out.
Yeah.
So how about I just generate a couple like this.
Um,
and I can send them to you all and you can post them.
And if it works and we can continue doing it.
And then at some point,
um,
we can find a way to automate them and so that they can be created for you.
And we can just kind of work through the process and see how it goes.
I'll work on generating a few more care cells like this and see how,
how that process works.
Does that sound okay?
Yeah.
That's perfect.
Okay.
Perfect.
And do you have examples of other websites that you've worked on?
Yeah.
I can send you,
um,
I can send you a couple.
I have been working for a life coach and then,
um,
uh,
private aviation company and then as well as like a run club company as well.
I can send you a few of their websites.
Um,
if that'd be helpful.
Thank you.
Of course.
I haven't reconstructed a website completely like I reconstructed your yours.
Um,
so I,
but I have,
um,
like gone through and changed websites based off of what the clients want.
Um,
so it's not like a full rebrand and it's not as drastic of a change,
but I can definitely show you some things that have been working on.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
This is also cool that you're doing this.
We love it.
You don't like it.
You're doing it in a while.
Like I told them you just doing it and you're just,
like it's kind of amazing what you're doing.
So thank you.
Thank you.
Well,
I'm very grateful for you all.
It's a really,
it's a great learning opportunity for me as well.
So I'm grateful that you're,
that you're trusting me and I'm so excited to be working with you all.
Thank you.
Um,
I'm a whole well.
Next steps.
I guess we need to send you the PDF.
Um,
and we will,
and we'll just kind of get together and write down everything that we sort of
everything that we sort of remember that we talked about and you have it recorded, so
if we forget something, you'll have it on there. And then, yeah, and then send us a couple
of those Instagram posts and we'll go from there. That sounds great. That sounds awesome.
Well, perfect. And then if there's anything else you all think about, feel free to just
let me know and we'll be in touch. Okay. All right. That sounds great. Thank you guys.
Have a great rest of your day. All right, you too. Bye. Bye.